Here are three things to watch out of Mondays open.
Memory stocks continue to rally to begin the trading week.
This morning, Needham raised Micron's price target to $1,550 to share from $500, saying
market fundamentals will remain stronger for longer due to continued demand.
Micron reports earnings this Wednesday.
While Spargo hiked its price targets across the semiconductor equipment space, boosting
ASML to $2,200, applied materials to $715, and KLA Corporate 2305 and land research to $450.
The analyst said it expects continued positive results in the second quarter.
In SpaceX is reportedly preparing a $20 billion bond offering.
The proceeds will refinance a borage loan that matures in September of 2027.
Be sure to download the Schwab Network app and watch 24-7 on SchwabNetwork.com.